(Sheldon:)...eleven.
(Sheldon:)It's a good thing
I didn't send that letter.
(Skype ringtone plays)
(Raj:)Mm. Hello, Daddy. What's up?
(Dr Koothrapalli:)Not much, just wanted to see
how my son's doing.
(Raj:)Very well, thank you.
(Dr Koothrapalli:)Are you still dating
that dermatologist?
(Raj:)If you could feel
how soft my skin is,
(Raj:)you wouldn't have to ask.
(Dr Koothrapalli:)Oh, and there's something else
I wanted to ask you.
(Dr Koothrapalli:)Why did you spend a month's rent
on a toy helicopter?!
(Raj:)Oh, you're where that bill goes.
(Dr Koothrapalli:)I'm tired of indulging
your foolish lifestyle.
(Dr Koothrapalli:)It's time you learned
responsibility.
(Dr Koothrapalli:)And the only way
to teach you that
(Dr Koothrapalli:)is to cut off your allowance.
No, Daddy, no!
(Raj:)There are lots of other ways
to teach me responsibility.
(Raj:)I know, you can give me an egg
(Raj:)and make me take care of it
for a week!
(Dr Koothrapalli:)No, my mind is made up.
(Dr Koothrapalli:)Starting now,
you're on your own.